Xiao Ting, can you handle spicy food?
I can.
Add a bit more, add more.
Add more.
By the way.
Here.
Okay, that's enough.
Xiao Mei isn't replying to my WeChat messages.
What's going on?
Well, it's like this.
Our place was shut down for restructuring, right?
So everyone lost their jobs.
Xiao Mei went back to her hometown in the country.
It's all my fault.
I caused everyone to lose their jobs.
I'll take a penalty drink.
I'll drink with you, Huilan.
Xiao Ting.
What are your plans for the future?
Me?
I've been working out here for almost half a year now.
And I realized...
I realized staying in school is better.
If you study,
you won't have to look for jobs like this anymore.
So I've decided.
I'm going back to study hard.
Studying is good.
You definitely need to study more.
When I was young,
I just didn't study enough.
Knowledge is a weapon.
Learn as much as you can.
Strap it to yourself.
One on the left, one on the right.
Only then will you realize
that when a girl is making her way in the world,
it comes in handy.
Then no one will dare to bully you.
Got it?
I got it, Huilan.
Thank you for everything you've done.
If it weren't for you,
I'd probably still be suffering in silence in that hellhole.
Thank you.
Stop with all that.
Me, I'm actually getting a bit emotional.
Hurry up and eat. It's on me today.
You're treating?
How can you treat without me?
Right?
Boss Jiang.
As soon as Huilan comes here,
you come over just to steal the spotlight.
Aren't you two...
both out of work now?
Right?
Come on.
Let's have a drink.
Drink up.
Aren't you embarrassed?
What do you mean by pouring so little?
If you want to show your sincerity,
remember what Wang Daren did last time?
Chug, chug it.
Fine.
I'll chug it today.
Keep going.
Come on.
Let's do another one.
See?
A man like this,
how can you count on him?
That son of a bitch can't even outdrink me.
Boss Jiang is such a lightweight.
Huilan,
I... I'm actually not very good with words.
But I really appreciate your help.
Everything I want to say is in this drink.
Thank you.
Are you heading back to your hometown tomorrow?
You don't have to worry about me.
If I get the chance,
I'll definitely come back to visit you.
Xiao Ting.
Here.
Take this.
This is...
Huilan.
You have to take it.
No, Huilan.
Listen to me, you need to take it.
Don't...
Don't be like this.
You have to study hard.
You hear me?
Only with a good education
can you boldly step out into the world.
I believe
you'll definitely make a name for yourself.
I'm going to miss you so much.
Remember to come back and visit me.
You'll always be the best big sister to me.
All right.
Okay.
Face life with a smile.
I'll walk you to a cab.
Okay.
Let's go to the gate and get a ride
and head home.
Old Li.
I've got something to do.
Watch my stall for a bit.
Okay.
Don't worry.
Thanks.
Where are you going?
We're here.
Why bring me to a cornfield in the middle of the night?
Drop the act.
I know you're not drunk.
You figured it out.
Men know men best.
I know you're up to no good with Huilan.
I'm warning you.
Don't get any ideas about her.
You're quite overprotective, aren't you?
Me? Do I really look like such a bad guy?
I don't care if you look like one or not.
Just get out of the car.
You're just gonna leave?
Wait.
Hey!
I'm still your boss, you know.
Not after work, you're not.
Remember to return the hat tomorrow.
The hat?
Hat?
What is this place?
My...
My phone's dead too!
Hey,
wait,
don't go!
My phone's dead!
What am I supposed to do?
Li Yiran!
Come out!
Where are you?
Stop yelling.
Look at the time. You're waking the neighbors.
I brought you some good food.
Uncle Daren grilled it for you.
You drank again.
No, I didn't.
I can smell it.
Impossible.
Look how straight I'm walking.
You're always so stubborn.
I have something to tell you.
Perfect.
I have something to tell you too.
You go first then.
I got a job offer from a company in Shanghai.
They want me to start at the end of the month.
This company...
Is one I've always really wanted to work for.
That's great news.
But I'm still hesitating.
Why are you hesitating?
You've lived in Shanghai for so many years.
If it weren't for me...
Holding you back...
You'd have been promoted and rich there long ago.
Why hesitate?
Just go.
I'm just afraid you'll cause trouble if I leave.
What kind of trouble could I cause?
Me, I've got hands and feet, and I'm smart too.
I don't need you watching me every day.
You don't need me watching you?
Then let me remind you of all the messes you've made.
Hurry up and eat. Just eat.
While it's hot.
It'll get cold soon.
Here's some chili powder too.
Didn't you say you had something to tell me?
What is it?
I just wanted to tell you...
I...
Passed my probation.
My job will be stable from now on.
And my income will be stable too.
That's great.
Yeah.
You should still take my bankbook.
I don't have any use for it anyway.
When you get to Shanghai...
You'll need to rent a place...
And order takeout.
Take it.
Is this what you wanted to say?
Just this.
No need for that.
As for your money...
Just keep it for yourself.
I'll be making 15k a month there.
And I get double pay at the end of the year.
How much is 15k?
Fifteen thousand.
That much?
Then we definitely have to celebrate.
Pure draft.
You know?
I don't usually bring this out to drink.
Cheers.
Bottoms up.
That's right.
What are you saving that for?
To raise fish?
You gonna raise fish in it?
I'm heading out.
I'm off to work.
I'll cook tonight.
Come home for dinner after work.
Alright, alright, alright.
Hurry up, hurry up!
He's crying, he's crying!
Hoeing fields in the midday sun,
Sweat drips into the soil below.
Ugly freak!
Give me candy!
Who knows that the food on our plates,
Every grain comes from hard work.
Ugly freak!
Well, uh...
your luck...
I'm sorry.
You don't have a job anymore. Why are you out all day?
Now that I don't have a job,
pretending to have one...
is what's really exhausting.
When will the seasons ever end?
Three meals of barbecue a day.
Who's calling?
Who is it?
It's Yiran.
You take it, you take it.
Okay.
Hello? What's up?
Wu Huilan, I've told you so many times.
You need to put your toothbrush back after using it.
Or else you won't find it next time.
Got it, got it.
And what about your...
work uniform?
Why is it in the bathroom?
My work uniform?
My company issued us a new set.
I have something to wear.
Don't worry about it.
Why is it so noisy over there?
I... I... I...
I'm in the bathroom.
Someone next to me is washing their hands.
They're waiting for me to give them a massage.
Alright, alright.
I'll hang up now.
A massage? You...
Every single one of them
hangs up before I can even finish speaking.
So rude.
Are you really not going to
tell Yiran that you lost your job?
What is there to say?
She's going back to Shanghai next week anyway.
I'll just drift wherever life takes me.
Yiran is still young.
A bright future is waiting for her.
My job loss has to stay a secret.
Make sure you don't let it slip.
Don't worry.
My lips
are sealed tight.
I'm so annoyed.
Grab me a beer.
You promised Yiran you'd stop drinking.
If you get drunk, how will you explain it to her?
Just one glass.
Look at this sky.
It's exactly like my mood.
It comes and goes just like that.
Yiran,
are you really planning to go back to Shanghai?
Yeah.
It's a rare opportunity.
Wu Huilan found a job too,
so it's about time I headed back.
I don't want you to go.
Once you leave,
who knows when you'll be back next.
For the New Year!
I'll definitely come back for the New Year.
Don't lie to me.
Really.
A lone shadow on the cold river,
an old friend in the martial world.
Meeting by chance, why must we have met before?
Chen Baixi,
why are you being so sentimental?
Are you afraid I'll run off without paying you?
How is that possible?
I never planned to ask you for that money.
What's mine is mine.
Once I return to Shanghai,
our debt will be paid off soon.
Yo, bro.
Nice acting this time.
I could even see the reluctance to part in your eyes.
After all, Xiaoxitian is losing half its sky.
Bro.
In everything you do,
you can't always rely on others.
I believe
with you and Xiaofang working together,
Xiaoxitian will definitely get better and better.
Don't try to comfort me.
Everyone has their own ambitions.
Everyone has their own path to take.
Those involved are blind.
Detachment brings wisdom.
Outsiders see things clearly.
Stop right there.
I hate listening to you bookworms talk.
Speak like a normal person.
Listening to you is exhausting.
But I just love listening to you talk.
I love listening to whatever you say, Chen Xiaofang.
Li Yiran,
you silly woman...
You just love saying these things.
But I really don't want you to go.
Come here.
Recently,
police in many areas solved a major child trafficking case.
The criminal gang often pretended to ask for directions,
offer help, or give gifts
to approach children playing alone.
The police disclosed
that the gang was highly organized,
using fake plates to commit crimes across regions,
greatly increasing the difficulty of the investigation.
Station commentator and criminologist Professor Li noted
that such cases
highlight the importance of guardianship in public spaces.
He also urged schools and communities to work together
to raise awareness against trafficking
and make anti-trafficking education a regular practice.
Fucking human traffickers.
Their kids will definitely be born without assholes.
Huilan,
it's almost time to get off work.
Careful, your kid might see you.
What are you laughing at?
What's so funny? Seriously.
If my Yiran finds me,
like you guys said,
me, I'll just...
I know!
"Tear my mouth wide open!"
My ears have calluses from hearing it!
Xi Wa!
Time to go home!
Where did you go?
Why won't you listen?
Go home with Grandma.
Xi Wa!
Where did you go?
What's wrong with her?
The old lady's grandson,
was lost here twenty years ago.
So pitiful.
These human traffickers really are...
Me, if I caught them, I'd slice them to pieces,
chop them up,
and feed them to the dogs!
If you ask me,
the ones left alive
suffer even more.
That's true.
Look,
look at her, she's so pitiful.
She's so old and all alone.
Grandma can't find you!
Xi Wa!
Go home!
So pitiful.
What time is it?
I'm leaving.
It's still early.
Getting off work soon. Gotta go, gotta go.
Hang out a bit longer.
Just a bit longer.
No, I'm done.
You two chat.
Yangyang, let's go home.
Huilan.
What a cute fishy!
I want it.
You want it?
Sure.
Boss!
Come here for a second.
Okay.
Get a fish for us.
Which one do you want?
That one.
All right, this one.
Here.
What are you afraid of?
These fish are raised to be killed and eaten.
But Yaya...
Yaya can't be eaten.
Yaya is a pet.
Yaya is meant to be kept.
This kind of fish is meant to be eaten.
All right, all right.
If you're scared to look, just turn around.
Yangyang, listen to your godmother.
Being scared is useless.
A lot of things,
just because you like them,
doesn't mean they'll stay with you forever.
Just like your mom and me,
we both will get old.
We can't stay by your side forever.
Once you grow up,
you have to learn to face things yourself.
You need to be a bit braver.
Got it?
There, there.
Come here, give your godmother a hug.
You're so silly. Why are you crying?
There, stop crying.
Sweetie.
Here's some tea for your dad.
My dad said...
they're this year's...
first harvest.
You know quite a lot about tea.
I recognize this box.
It's a lychee vine pattern.
Right.
It symbolizes endless life...
and prosperity.
They print this on urns, too.
What...
What do you mean by that?
However...
it's a bit heavier than an urn.
The material is quite nice.
We are...
on a blind date.
How could you say...
this is an urn?
Why are you crying?
Here, here.
Xiao... Xiaofang?
Your conversation is so touching.
Please, continue.
We're on a blind date.
Who are you?
So you're on a blind date.
My apologies, I'm sorry.
If I may ask...
do you two have any...
plans to get married?
We just met.
We still need to get to know each other better.
Right. Who gets married on the first date?
Getting to know him is easy.
Just ask me.
I'm his ex-wife.
What?
You were married?
Divorced.
We're still in the divorce cooling-off period.
Married and divorced?
Why go on a blind date if you're married?!
You scumbag!
I'm on a blind date because I got divorced!
So you really like blind dates?
No.
Xiaofang, you know me.
I'm just doing this to appease my dad.
No need to explain it to me.
I don't want to hear it.
Xiaofang, are you jealous?
What a joke.
Why would be jealous?
Good. That's good.
Young Master Zhou.
You're quite capable now.
Today you can go on a blind date to appease your dad...
tomorrow,
to fulfill your filial duty,
you could kick me, Chen Xiaofang, out of the house.
If I, Zhou Fang, were that kind of person...
I'd get hit by bird poop the moment I walk out!
Why not swear to be struck by lightning?
Wipe it yourself.
Being struck by lightning works too!
Xiaofang!
Xiao...
I've never seen karma strike so fast.
Don't swear oaths so recklessly from now on.
This world has finally gone mad.
Miss, care to check out our tour packages?
Seven days and nights, originally 3,999.
Now, it's only 99.
It's a rare opportunity.
This isn't a scam, is it?
Don't worry, miss.
We're a legitimate travel agency.
All of our tour routes
are carefully selected.
Great landscapes,
and a tour guide.
If it really is 99,
then that's not bad.
In all my life,
I've never gone on a proper trip.
Here, sign me up.
I'll sign up.
I'll go too.
Huilan, what a coincidence.
Is it?
I live right here.
Just passing by.
I happen to need a getaway too.
So, we can go together.
And look out for each other.
Sign me up.
You guys know each other?
Since you know each other,
join together.
This is a seniors' tour.
You want to join too?
He's so handsome, romantic, and rich.
Huilan has really
struck some dumb luck.
More like bad luck, if you ask me.
With what he has to offer,
he could get any young girl he wants.
Why does he keep pestering Huilan?
I think there's something fishy going on.
No.
I can pay for myself.
I think you're a weasel greeting a chicken.
You're up to no good.
You...
Wang Daren!
Who are you calling a chicken?
I...
That's not what I meant.
I definitely didn't mean you.
I meant he's the weasel.
Huilan, he just doesn't know how to talk.
He meant that
he's afraid you'll get tricked by the weasel.
99 bucks, right?
I'll go too. Keep the change.
99 bucks for seven days and nights of fun?
Five-star hotels
and private chauffeurs?
And you believed that?
Why don't you just write 'I'm a scammer' on your face?
We are not scammers.
We're a legitimate travel agency.
You guys don't sound legitimate at all.
No, let me tell you,
there are tons of scammers like this nowadays.
They either claim it's free
or advertise something like 99 bucks.
It seems very cheap,
but they specifically target middle-aged folks like you.
99 bucks for seven days and seven nights?
That wouldn't even cover their transport costs.
Did they already pay?
Refund them immediately.
Or I'll call the cops right now.
Yeah, give us our money back.
Seven days and nights is too long.
I still have to work.
I can't take that much time off.
Come on, refund it, bro.
Refund mine too.
Refund it.
Refund what?
Hurry up.
Refund it.
I can't.
Just refund it.
Boss Jiang already paid for it a long time ago.
What?
You really are a flirtatious weasel.
No, don't get the wrong idea.
Huilan.
I actually just wanted to take you out to relax.
Mr. Jiang, you...
Why are you taking her out to relax?
Huilan lost her job.
Yangyang!
Shoo.
What?
Wu Huilan, you lost your job again?!
No, I didn't.
How could I possibly lose my job?
Leniency for those who confess, severity for those who resist.
You actually believe what Yangyang said?
I'm Angel Baby.
How could I possibly get fired?
Angel Baby, my ass.
Just tell me the truth.
Tell you what?
Where were you yesterday?
At the shop.
You left home at 7:00 a.m.
Why do your WeChat steps only show 278?
What the hell is this?
How did you know?
None of your business.
Uncle Daren...
He gave me a ride.
He drove me there and back.
I didn't walk.
Where's your uniform?
At the shop.
It wasn't confiscated by the shop, right?
How is that possible?
I'll bring it back to show you tomorrow.
How much did you get paid this month?
3,800. I already told you.
3,800? I checked your bank statement.
You didn't get paid at all.
That's because the boss delayed my pay.
I'll get it in a couple of days.
Fine.
What's the new shop next to Yunshui Pavilion?
A bun shop.
What's their specialty?
Vermicelli buns.
What drinks do they sell?
Soy milk.
Soy milk? Isn't it coffee?
They have coffee, too.
Coffee, my ass.
No shop opened at all. I was tricking you.
You...
Me, you set me up!
Crazy.
Still eating?
Are you really that hungry?
You still have an appetite after losing your job?
The reason?
Spit it out.
I reported the boss.
You reported the boss?
Are you crazy?
Crazy? Why would I be crazy?
Son of a bitch. That client was a pervert.
He was getting handsy with our technician.
And our boss was an accomplice.
He took that pervert's side.
Me, you know my temper.
I dragged them straight to the police station.
I was wrong, okay?
I shouldn't have meddled.
This time, you were right to.
You did good.
What do you mean?
What I mean is...
You protected a coworker this time.
You stood up for what's right.
Great job.
But from now on, which jobs you can take,
and which you can't,
you need to use your best judgment, got it?
Alright, eat up.
What do you mean?
It's so sour. Me, I've been sick of it for ages.
Zhou Fang,
I feel a bit bad asking this,
but I'll just get straight to the point.
Go ahead.
I wanted to ask you
if Wu Huilan could come work here.
Any job will do.
Who?
Wu Huilan.
Li Yiran,
I've helped you with everything I could.
Your mom is an industry jinx.
You can't do this to me!
She ruins every industry she works in.
It's not like I don't know that.
Young Boss Zhou!
What do you mean?
Say it to my face!
Why are you badmouthing me behind my back?
Wu Huilan.
What did we just agree on?
Go wait for me outside.
I'm sorry, Auntie Huilan.
Zhou Fang,
I heard you were expanding your business,
so you must need more hands, right?
But I don't need your mom.
Your mom is a professional mourner and brawler.
What could she possibly do here?
Be a cleaner!
Sure.
Well...
I mean, Li Yiran,
just to get your mom a job,
you really threw away your principles.
Then I'll just call Xiaofang.
You can ask her about my principles.
She can start immediately.
Thanks, Zhou Fang.
I owe you a big favor, and I'll definitely repay you.
But let me be clear up front.
She has to follow the company rules.
Whether she can stay or not
depends entirely on Auntie Huilan herself.
Of course, of course.
I just came to get her an interview.
Then,
about Xiaofang and me...
Don't worry. I'll put in a good word for you.
Wu Huilan!
Here!
About your job,
we can't waste a single minute.
I'll leave her to you.
I'm going to find Xiaofang.
I'm off.
Young Boss Zhou.
Hello.
Um...
I even brought my apron.
I can start as a cleaner.
You're going to be a cleaner anyway.
What were you thinking?
Go polish all the shoes in the shop first.
Shining shoes.
Fine. Me, I've done it all.
Shining shoes is nothing.
288,000!
My mom said not a penny less.
Your mom gave me 188,000.
What does she take me for?
A few days ago, because of this,
my mom was hospitalized!
Didn't we go over budget on the renovations?
Please, you two, calm down.
Don't be mad, don't be mad.
Within my limited scope of responsibilities,
I'll throw in a package deal for you.
You shut up!
Okay.
If your family doesn't give me the bride price now,
I'm not getting married!
Then don't!
Just to buy a house,
we've already spent all our family's savings!
For this 188,000 bride price,
my parents had to beg and borrow everywhere!
Are you trying to drive my family to death?
Are you trying to drive me to death now?
What's with the yelling? Are you cockfighting?
Who are you?
Are you two collecting debts?
Or are you asking for a bride price?
None of your damn business!
I'm so sorry, you two.
This is our company's new cleaning lady.
Leave now. You don't have a say here.
I really can't listen to this anymore.
It's so frustrating!
You two, turn around.
Your mom, his mom.
Are your two moms getting married,
or are you two getting married?
Your mom...
Don't swear.
Don't fight.
Come here for a sec, sis.
Calm down, calm down.
Calm down.
On your big day, why are you pouting?
Let me ask you. Do you want to marry him,
or do you just want his money?
My mom said,
if the money isn't right, the attitude isn't right.
If the attitude isn't right, the person isn't right.
Marriage is about two people living together.
It's not a business deal with a scale.
You're asking him for so much bride price,
then let me ask you,
how much dowry did your family prepare for you?
My family prepared 88,000.
Come here
Come over, sit down
Young man,
this dowry
is the bride's family's backing,
and this bride price
is the respect from the groom's family.
Whether it's the bride price or the dowry,
they both represent the parents' goodwill.
It's their hope that after you two get married,
you will live a good life together.
Here's what I think.
The bride price is 88,000.
The dowry is 88,000.
Both families prosper together.
As for the rest, when you have a baby in the future,
you can make up the difference at the one-month celebration.
It's truly not easy being parents.
Right?
Why make it hard for everyone?
This way, everyone is happy.
Isn't that right?
I think what she said makes a lot of sense.
Honey, whatever you say goes.
Young man,
you must make up the rest of the dowry later.
Otherwise, Auntie here will be the first to raise hell with your family.
Don't worry, sis.
I'll go tell my mom right now.
Come back.
Then you'll have to get me another wedding dress.
Sure, that's a very simple request.
What is your name?
Go arrange it for them quickly.
Whatever you like, as many dresses as you want.
Xu Wumei.
Just go when you're told to.
Then please step this way, you two.
Go straight ahead and turn right.
Thank you, sis.
No problem at all.
This way, please.
Go on, hurry up.
She's so nice.
Just you wait.
Auntie Huilan.
Boss Zhou.
I see you really have a way with words.
You're not suited for cleaning.
From now on, you will be our company's
marriage consultant.
What's a marriage consultant?
A matchmaker.
Matchmaker?
What do you mean, matchmaker?
Me? I'm a marriage consultant.
Got it?
What marriage consultant?
Why does marriage need a consultant?
It sounds like a scam.
In this world,
you create your own title.
This time around,
Me, I'm definitely going to shine.
Work hard.
You can go back to Shanghai with peace of mind.
I won't lose my job again.
As long as you don't get fired,
I'll be thanking the heavens.
Before you go, there's a job.
I'll send you the address.
Tomorrow morning at 8:00. Be there or be square.
Mr. Chen.
Be there or be square.
Before you go, there's a job.
Tomorrow morning at 8:00.
Be there or be square.
You ignored the "job at 8:00" part
and only saw "be there or be square."
I didn't notice.
But then again, I think
Mr. Chen is actually a pretty good guy.
Just look at him.
He's so tall,
and he looks so sharp.
If you get together with him in the future,
get married, and have a baby,
the kid would probably be quite pretty.
Are you okay?
I've told you a million times.
Stop trying to play matchmaker.
I'm an excellent judge of character.
Besides, I'm a marriage consultant now. A professional.
You two
kind of look like a couple.
Really, really.
It's not on them, and it's not at home.
Where the hell is the bracelet?
It was the same with the old man at the last place.
He was dead for half a month before anyone noticed.
It wasn't until the neighbors smelled the stench
that they realized he was gone.
His kids showed up just to look for cash and bankbooks.
A bunch of ungrateful bastards.
In this day and age,
everyone is completely blinded by money.
Mom.
Where did you put the bracelet, Mom?
Mr. Chen,
this isn't right.
What's wrong with it?
She's my mom.
Respect the dead.
Let's go.
Steady.
Let the gongs and drums echo through the mountains.
May white cranes guide your way to the West.
Lay down the earthly toils of this life.
May your path to the netherworld be free of storms.
The police came last night.
It's so tragic.
Steady now.
The hearse is right downstairs.
How long has she been dead?
I don't know.
It's so tragic.
She's been dead for a while.
It smells awful.
Her kid is so unfilial.
Before your mother passed away,
she made you some dumplings,
and chili sauce.
This bracelet...
When my mom got married,
my dad gave it to her.
After my dad passed away,
my mom raised me all by herself.
After college, I was assigned to work in Qinghai.
My mom didn't want to go that far with me.
She said,
she'd stay wherever my dad was.
That bracelet was all she had left of my dad.
I found this bracelet to bury it with her,
so she and my dad
could be buried together.
We had a misunderstanding earlier.
I thought once I made enough money,
I could return home a success.
But...
I'm a failure.
Sir...
My mom... my mom never enjoyed a day of comfort.
She never had a single good day.